[{"answer": "I got us tickets to see my friend tomorrow", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Ally, I don't want to go either, but my friend told my friend he'd go, and I'm not going by myself", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "How'd you get this number", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What do you want", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You don't know a fuckin' thing. Come by my apartment tonight, we'll figure this out", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Ain't like what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No. But thanks for asking", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend, I told you, drugs are for losers", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "But it's okay to drink", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "How old are you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "When you're older it'll be okay", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Old enough", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No I haven't", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He caught somethin'? What the hell did he catch", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Shit", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I didn't do shit", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Just take her back to our place", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He threw us out?", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "She'll be alright. You didn't hit us that hard", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Fuck that, you'll have all kinds 'a problems if we do that. Cops, insurance and whatnot. You probably got drugs on you..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Oye, don't get mad, but would you be mad if I try to fuck your sister", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Maybe you think you can talk to her for me", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend's waiting", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You didn't snap", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Car", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Maybe its just a rash, 'cause I don't have anything", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I can go to the doctor by myself. And if I have it, I got it from you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It hurt. I knew it would hurt, but that was kinda worse than I thought. Does Heather... like it", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "She doesn't? Why not", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "She never let's me do it", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I don't know. She does shave though. How come you don't shave", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "She doesn't? Why not", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I don't know. I don't want to. Do you love her", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't know. She does shave though. How come you don't shave", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I don't know. I don't want to. Do you love her", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "How can you not know", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I thought it was a bad match. It was my friend's idea", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You know what she thinks better than me", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Neither do I", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I wish you were. I don't like my friend", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Don't you like my friend", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Why not", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "He took too long for you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Ally, look, he's cheating on me, I know it in my heart, but I want him to admit it, alright? Before I fucking flush what's left of this shithole relationship down the toilet, I want him to admit it", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Fine", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Hey, listen, can I sleep on your couch", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Come on, mehn, we're in trouble here. We got thrown out of our home", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend's got couch", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You got evicted", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Who gives a shit? He moved out", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I gotta wash my hands", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "So what am I, a goddam marriage counselor", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "He hit you", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "No, he punched me. With his fist, a bunch 'a times", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I didn't do shit", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Did your parents call", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Okay... good. Thanks. Are you okay", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Really? A little girl like you. You think I might get you to share a little of that", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "If you do something nice for me, I might do something nice for you", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Make an offer", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Twelve hundred! That's nothing", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "See", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Before he fucking hit me", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Alright, you are mighty, mighty... not very nice when another girl is near your boyfriend", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": " I don't say those things", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Don't say nuts, don't say psycho, don'", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Yes you do! Yes you do", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": " I don't say those things", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "What I meant, I don't mean them. I meant that I don't mean them. That I don't mean to say them", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes you do! Yes you do", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Well, what do you mean", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Well what the hell can I do? There's nothin'. I got your goddam initials tattoo'd next to my balls", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "You don't like it?", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": " I'm not sure about that, RJ! Let's break out the chalk board, some X's and O's, an' make fer certain!  Just toss my friend out the fuckin' window", "docId": "Little-Athens.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": " These are my drugs,  That's your money", "qsentId": 78}]